

JESSICA NATIONS

WEB DEVELOPER | ST. LOUIS, MO

OBJECTIVE

Versatile Web Designer and Developer who consistently demonstrates a high attention to detail combined with a knowledge of Python, HTML, CSS, SQL, C#/ASP.Net, and an extensive customer service background seeks a position where experience, motivation, and commitment to excellence will be utilized.

SKILLS

programming languages:

- Python
- C#/ASP.Net

tools and technologies:

- GitHub
- MAMP
- Mogups
- Trello

IDE:

Visual Studio
database administration:

• SOL

EXPERIENCE

WAREHOUSE CLERK • CBRE • 10/2017 - PRESENT

I have helped to write and compile the manual explaining my job duties. I researched and helped order new mail carts. I created the training materials for X-Ray operation training.

CIRCULATION ASSISTANT AND LIBRARY CLERK • ST. LOUIS COUNTY LIBRARY • 06/2014 - 10/2017

I was one on a team of 3-5 librarians that did everything from creating library cards, providing customer assistance, shelving the materials, helping with library programs, and maintaining the sale shelf.

REPLENISHMENT SPECIALIST AND SALES ASSOCIATE • BANANA REPUBLIC FACTORY STORE • 02/2014 - 10/2017

I received employee excellence recognition multiple months in a row. I was known for being the hardest and most efficient worker in the store. My managers relied on me to help train new employees and new managers.

EDUCATION

LAUNCHCODE 101 • 06/2018 • LAUNCHCODE HEADQUARTERS

BACHELORS OF FINE ARTS DEGREE IN MUSIC HISTORY AND LITERATURE • 12/2011 • SIUE

MASTERS OF LIBRARY AND INFORMATION SCIENCE • 05/2013 • UNIVERSITY OF ILLINOIS URBANA-CHAMPAIGN







